var questions = [{
         "question": "What Year Did Taxi Drive Come Out?",
         "option1":"1981",
         "option2":"1984",
         "option3":"1976",
         "option4": "1966",
         "answer": "3"
    //first question is not loading
}, {
        "question": "What is  Taxi Driver name?",
        "option1": "MR.Cooper",
        "option2": "Travis Bickle",
        "option3": "Christopher Moltisanti",
        "option4": "Frank Rizzo",
        "answer": "2"
    
}, {
        "question": "What dose Taxi Driver like to eat?",
        "option1": "Steak",
        "option2": "Donuts",
        "option3":  "Apple Pie with a slice Of yellow cheese",
        "option4": "Fried Iceream And Anchovies",
        "answer": "3"
},{
        "question": "What city dose it take place in?",
        "option1": "New York City",
        "option2": "NEW Jersey",
        "option3": "Barcelona",
        "option4": "Chicago",
        "answer":  "1"

},{
        "question": "What can Taxi Driver use a 45 for?",
        "option1":"kill an Elephant",
        "option2":"To Shoot",
        "option3":"To Show Off",
        "option4":"Join The CIA",
        "answer": "1"

}, {
        "question": "What is Taxi Driver real name?",
        "option1": "Nicky Santoro",
        "option2": "Robert De niro",
        "option3": "Tony Soprrano",
        "option4": "Billy Bats",
        "answer": "2"

}, {
        "question": "What is Taxi Driver favoreit movie?",
        "option1": "Taxi Driver",
        "option2": "Saturday Night Fever",
        "option3": "Rocky",
        "option4": "Pornos",
        "answer": "4"
},{
        "question": "When can he work?",
        "option1": "Only Nights",
        "option2": "Any Time Any Where",
        "option3": "Only On Weekends",
        "option4": "Hollidays Only",
        "answer":  "2"
}, {
            "question": "What is Taxi Driver favoreit hair cut?",
            "option1": "Jerry Curl",
            "option2": "Hi and Tight",
            "option3": "Mohawk",
            "option4": "Slick Back",
            "answer": "3"
},{
            "question": "Whats is favorite candy?",
            "option1": "Jujubess",
            "option2": "Chocolate",
            "option3": "Jolly Ranchers",
            "option4": "Lemon Sherbert",
            "answer":  "1"



}
]